[Music]
welcome
to aehelp.com ielts test preparation
videos you now have a chance to face off
against ming lung from vietnam who again
gets a band
9 for his performance on the speaking
interview first you will do the
interview with me
i'm the examiner and you're the
candidate i will ask you the questions
you give me the answers use the
subtitles as necessary
i encourage you to try answering on your
own first
record your answers so that you can
compare them
to ming luns afterwards
make sure to visit and join our premium
package
at aehelp.com where you will find
practice exams video lessons and a fully
interactive course
you can use this discount code to save
also in the video description
now watch and learn
welcome to the speaking section of the
ielts exam my name is adrian
and i will be your examiner for this
part of the test
the speaking has three parts i will give
you instructions for each
and i'm going to record this for marking
purposes
what is your full name
may i see your identification please
brendan
thank you okay
here is your passport back for part one
i will ask you a couple more questions
to get to know you better and some
questions
on a general topic do you work or study
what do you like about your work or
school
let's talk about friends how often do
you meet your friends
what do you usually do with your friends
where did you meet your best friend
how do you keep in touch with your
friends
have the games you played with your
friends changed in the last 10 years
if you could give a gift to one of your
friends
what would you give and who would you
give it to
that is the end of part one now we will
continue with part two
for part two here is a card with some
questions on it
there's some note paper and a pencil in
front of you
you will have one minute to look at the
questions think about your answers
take notes in the one minute if you wish
and then you will have two minutes to
speak
i will tell you when to start when to
stop
okay brenden your one minute preparation
time is up please begin speaking
welcome to the speaking portion of the
ielts exam my name is adrian i will be
your examiner
for this section of the test it has
three parts i will give you
instructions for each and i'm going to
record this
for marking purposes
to begin i will ask you a few questions
to get to know you better and some
questions on a general topic
what is your full name my given names
are mingling
and my surname is zoong but please just
call me by my what's your nickname
it's brandon okay brandon may i see your
identification please
yes of course here's my passport which i
use for registration
thank you
okay good there's your passport back
do you work or study i currently work
part-time as a cashier
in a supermarket and i'm also studying
for this ies exam
so that i can continue my master's in
accounting studies next year in
california what do you like about your
work or school
i like my co-workers in my fairway
supermarket they're funny and kind
some of them have become good friends
let's talk about friends how often do
you meet your friends
the ones from work like dan and lisa i
meet almost every day
and some of my friends i hang out with
at the weekends
so quite often for sure what do you
usually do with your friends
during the workday evenings i usually
go to a coffee shop with my friends to
chat for an hour so
on the weekends we go to nature like the
high class saturday with lisa where did
you meet your best friend
i have to think about that for a moment
i met my best friend mike
at a music festival back in 2009 that my
parents took us to
he was hanging out near the main stage
between shows and i bumped into him
there
how do you keep in touch with your
friends
i keep in touch both face-to-face
and through digital media like messenger
whatsapp
email or simply just texting
have the games you play with your
friends changed in the past
10 years the games i play with my
friends
have certainly changed whether i think
about
the outdoor ones like basketball or
soccer
or inner ones like the games
we used to play on console they have
certainly changed
nowadays i'm more into tennis and board
games
i like the novelty of these if you
could give a gift to one of your friends
what would you give and who would you
give it to
given the opportunity to
give the friend i would
buy a new motorbike for mike because
i know which one he wants and it's his
birthday coming up in a couple of weeks
that's the end of part one now we will
continue with part two for part two here
is a card with some questions a pencil
and here is some note paper
you will have one minute to look at the
questions on the card
think about your answers take notes in a
minute if you wish
and then you will have two minutes to
speak i will tell you when to start
when to stop are you ready yep
okay go ahead turn over the card with
the questions your one minute
preparation begins now
brendan your one minute preparation time
is up please begin
speaking one of the most successful days
i had recently
was this past summer in july when i took
part
in an emergency rescue effort to help
save the lives of animals
that had been trapped by the oil for
parts 2 and parts 3 of this speaking
interview to practice
and to see minlung's band 9 make sure to
visit and join
our premium package at aehealth.com
where you will find original practice
exams
as well as a fully interactive course
and remember
to use this discount code also in the
video description
to get 10 percent off our premium
package
begin learning for success today
subscribe to our channel click over here
watch another video
click right up here and click our ielts
hero
to join our premium package and get
access to all of our videos
practice exams and a fully interactive
course